

WEB DEVELOPER

## **Details**

2014968838 ben@bytebug.io

#### Skills

MERN Stack

**RESTful API** 

**JavaScript** 

**j**Query

HTML & CSS

Python

CRUD

Git

## Languages

Spanish

#### **Hobbies**

Linux and open source enthusiast. Passionate about all computer related material. Pen testing and cyber security

## **Profile**

My primary goal is to apply my technical expertise all throughout the full software life cycle to ensure production and delivery of products and services that meet client specifications. Along with a competent software developing team, and with strong personal knowledge, skills, and experience in web development, I am confident that this goal can be achieved.

# **Employment History**

## Manager, Vocelli, Midlothian

JULY 2021 - PRESENT

- · Effectively controlled budgets and optimized expenses.
- Managed complex customer requests from contact to completion.
- Answered all customer queries with friendliness and expertise.
- Effectively led company functions and departments as designated.

## Software Quality Assurance, Metro West Call Center, Orlando

DECEMBER 2018 - NOVEMBER 2020

- Performed thorough mid-process inspections to ensure quality assurance.
- Followed policies and procedures related to application methods and quality standards at all times.

#### Call Center Rep, Alpine Acess/Sykes

FEBRUARY 2013 - JULY 2020

- Provided customers with top of the line service by working on an "on call" basis for emergencies and repairs.
- Maintained call center database by collecting and recording information.

# **Education**

#### Coding Bootcamp, University of Richmond, Richmond

NOVEMBER 2021 - MAY 2022

Graduated Top of Class with A-

## Business Studies, Universidad Dr. Jose Matias Delgado, San Salvador

JUNE 2009 - DECEMBER 2012

**Bilingual Studies** 

#### Courses

CS50, HarvardX

JANUARY 2022 - PRESENT

## JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures, Udemy

FEBRUARY 2022 - MAY 2022

# References

Jim Doyle from Div Strong

(804) 315-9609

Jay Thomas from Web Developer

jay@gfax.ch